[{"category":"Food & Drink","id":"639898395c9a75021f310466","correctAnswer":"Cabernet Sauvignon","incorrectAnswers":["Pinot Noir","Chardonnay","Merlot"],"question":"What is the most widely planted grape variety in the world?","tags":["food_and_drink","wine","drink"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"hard","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"Science","id":"622a1c3f7cc59eab6f952353","correctAnswer":"Willow","incorrectAnswers":["Birch","Elm","Cypress"],"question":"Aspirin was originally obtained from the bark of which tree?","tags":["chemistry","plants","medicine","science"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"hard","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"Film & TV","id":"622a1c377cc59eab6f95042b","correctAnswer":"Clarence","incorrectAnswers":["Terrence","Horace","Boris"],"question":"In the 1946 film, It's a Wonderful Life, what's the name of George Bailey's guardian angel?","tags":["film_and_tv"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"hard","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"Film & TV","id":"625fd704dc0dd3b72da64d1c","correctAnswer":"2007","incorrectAnswers":["2005","2009","2011"],"question":"In which year was There Will Be Blood first released in the cinema?","tags":["film","film_and_tv"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"hard","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"Geography","id":"62373f86cb85f7ce9e949ca1","correctAnswer":"Bahamas","incorrectAnswers":["Vanuatu","Peru","Kiribati"],"question":"Nassau is the capital city of which country?","tags":["capital_cities","geography"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"hard","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"Sport & Leisure","id":"622a1c367cc59eab6f9500a8","correctAnswer":"An Ice Skating Rink","incorrectAnswers":["A Football Pitch","A Tennis Court","A Rugby Pitch"],"question":"In the world of sport what has the maximum dimensions of 60 metres by 30 metres?","tags":["sport"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"hard","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"Arts & Literature","id":"622a1c3b7cc59eab6f9513d9","correctAnswer":"The Hunger Games","incorrectAnswers":["Voyages Extraordinaires","Harry Potter","Mortal Engines Quartet"],"question":"In which book series does 'Katniss Everdeen' appear?","tags":["young_adult","literature","fictitious_characters","general_knowledge","arts_and_literature"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"easy","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"Science","id":"622a1c377cc59eab6f950521","correctAnswer":"sacred texts","incorrectAnswers":["a variant of physiognomy","relationships within families particularly with a view to constructing family trees","waves or wave motions"],"question":"What is Hierographology the study of?","tags":["words","science"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"hard","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"Arts & Literature","id":"622a1c397cc59eab6f950f9a","correctAnswer":"William Shakespeare","incorrectAnswers":["Arthur C. Clarke","Isaac Newton","Enid Blyton"],"question":"Which author wrote 'Macbeth'?","tags":["arts_and_literature"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"easy","regions":[],"isNiche":false},{"category":"Arts & Literature","id":"622a1c367cc59eab6f95019b","correctAnswer":"Henry VIII","incorrectAnswers":["Richard III","Henry VII","James IV"],"question":"In 1526 Hans Holbein became the official portrait painter of which english king?","tags":["art","people","painting","uk","kings","arts_and_literature"],"type":"Multiple Choice","difficulty":"hard","regions":[],"isNiche":false}]
